AMAN SAINI

Jaipur, Rajasthan, India



amansaini19.012@gmail.com





linkedin.com/in/aman-saini-824140204

GITHUB Profile

https://github.com/AmanSaini07?tab=repositories

Summary

I Am a Engineering Student, pursuing my Bachelor's in Computer Science and Engineering from Modern Institute of Technology and Research Center. I am a Data Analyst, Python Programmer having vast knowledge of Python, SQL, Web-Scraping, Mongo DB, Data Cleaning, Data Visualizations through (Python, Excel and Tableau). Currently, I have 10 months experience in Data Analytics.

Experience



K Data Analyst Intern

ComicSense.xyz Jaipur, Rajasthan Apr 2022 - Present (4 months +)



Data Analyst Intern

Society for health and medical technology Noida, Uttar Pradesh Jul 2021 - Jan 2022 (7 months)

Education

MITRC College, Alwar

B.TECH, Computer ScienceAug 2019 - Jul 2023

Step by Step Public School

March 2004 - April 2019

Licenses & Certifications

Python Certification by Coginitive_Classes SQL Certification by Coginitive_Classes Microsoft Excel Certification by Udemy Google Data Analytics Professional certificate

Skills

- Python
- ❖ SQL
- ❖ Microsoft Excel
- * Tableau Visualization Tool
- Cleaning Data
- Django
- ❖ MongoDB
- ❖ Web-Scraping
- Data Visualization
- Data Mining